Guide to the North Carolina Mutual Life Insurance Company Archives, 1850-2008 and undated, bulk 1898-2008
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library Duke University Durham, N.C., USA
- Social Groups and Events Series, 1922-1992 and undated, (1 box)
  - Tuesday Morning Study Club
    - Minutes, 1962-1977, (2 folders)
    - Correspondence and memorabilia, 1966-1977
    - Agendas and readings, 1973-1976
    - Meeting materials on club topic, "The Great Transition," 1977
  - Glee Club history and programs, 1922 and undated
  - "Hayti Lived Before" (stage play, circa 1992) and the June 28, 1952 issue of The Nation